<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="SunGlasses" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="SunGlasses" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="Graphic Mod for control settings related to Sun Lighting effects" />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>
    ## SunGlasses

    This mod focus on solving under-exposure effects in vanilla CS2 game when facing the sun. \
    Options to adjust sun &amp; sky &amp; exposure settings, includes:

    - Sun disk size
    - Sun bloom
    - Enable/Disbale lens flare when facing sun
    - Sky exposure
    - Daytime Ambient lighting control
    - Dark area exposure brighten

    ### Sun disk size

    Sliding the bar to adjust the size of the sun disk

    ### Sun Bloom

    Adjust the sun bloom strength. It actually overrides the Blooms settings in PhotoMode, which means other artifical light bloom will also be affected.

    ### Lens Flare

    Option to toggle sun light lens flare effect when facing the sun

    ### Sky Exposure

    This option can adjust the sky exposure. Higher value will also brighten everything and reduce the impact ratio from sun light in the final view of the scene.

    ### Ambient Lighting

    Behave likes those mods with shadow strength adjustment / ambient lighting in CS1, but only affects daytime lighting.
    High value will make shadow lookes more blue (Because most of ambient lighting comes from sky)

    ### Dark Area Exposure

    This options controls the auto exposure behaivour in game. High Level will keeps dark area bright enough, but cause birghter area over-exposed (such as sky or sun)

    ### NOTES

    Sun Bloom Settings in mod will overwrite the effects in PhotoMode,
    but Sky Exposure &amp; Dark Area Exposure will affect nothings. They work independently
  </LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="" />
	<Tag Value="CodeMod" />
  <Tag Value="Graphics" />
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<ModVersion Value="1.0" />
	<GameVersion Value="1.0.*" />
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<ChangeLog Value="" />
  <ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/Cmyna/SunGlasses" />
</Publish>
